On a a fluidic level, initially, this phase of congestion linked to the reorganization
流体的な観点から見ると、当初、この再編成に伴う鬱血の段階は、
of my mesoderm
私の間葉の
in relation to my neural tube, which means there is a trajectory that will cause a concentration
私の神経管に対して、ある軌道があり、それが集中をもたらすことになります。
upwards,
上に向かって、
will bring up, here, primitive angiogenic cells
ここ、上部に血管新生細胞をもたらします。
that will concentrate.
原始的なものが集中します。
This whole process leads to a cardiac tube which, initially, is a primitive aortic tube
このプロセス全体は、当初は原始的な大動脈管であった心臓管をもたらします。
on the left and on the right,
左右に、
to concentrate due to the differential growth rate between the inner tissue
内部組織と外部組織の間の異なる成長速度によって集中し、胚の屈曲を引き起こします。
This flexion movement will bring the aortas towards the center.
この屈曲運動により、大動脈は中心に向かって移動します。
This meeting of the two aortas towards the center will also be the yellow to form the heart.
中心に向かう2つの大動脈のこの出会いは、心臓を形成するための黄色でもあります。
So it's a whole combination.
つまり、それは全体の組み合わせです。
I have it from my coccyx on the precardiac area which is here and which initially was
私は尾骨からここにある心臓前領域までそれを持っています。そしてそれは当初は
there
そこにありました
before I had the brain development movement.
脳の発達運動が始まる前です。
Initially, two aortas, through the developing neural tube, which has the motor,
当初、発達する神経管によって2つの大動脈があり、それが原動力となっています。
the amniotic cavity, enormous around it,
その周りには巨大な羊膜腔があり、
and the differential growth rate of my aortas, come closer to my median line, in front of
そして私の大動脈の異なる成長速度は、私の正中線に向かって、脊索の前に近づいてきます。
the notochord.
脊索。
These two tubes here, over time, come together towards the median line,
これら2つの管は、時間とともに正中線に向かって出会います。
like this.
このように。
And here, normally, there is a kind of inner tissue, specific.
そしてここには、通常、特定の内部組織があります。
Here, nutritive, if I no longer have this meeting, this inner tissue here,
もし私がこの出会いを失うと、ここにあるこの内部組織は栄養失調になります。
I have a corrosion field that will appear.
腐食の場が現れるでしょう。
There will be a connection little by little.
少しずつ接続ができていくでしょう。
This first meeting point here will give a structuring of the beginning of the heart.
ここでの最初の出会いの点は、心臓の初期の構造化をもたらします。
So it's a meeting on the median line of these two levels.
つまり、これら2つのレベルの正中線での出会いです。
But don't forget that you have to see it from the outside in.
しかし、これを外側から内側へと見る必要があることを忘れないでください。
If we start from the beginning, I see here a layer of cells that we will call...
最初からやり直すと、ここに細胞の層が見えます。
layer that was above the heart because if now I make an image before it is necessary
心臓の上にあった層です。なぜなら、もし今、私がその前に画像を作成するなら、
to really see this stretched like this, this tissue that is here is already a tissue that we call the
このように張られたものとして見る必要があります。ここにあるこの組織は、すでに私たちが呼ぶ組織です。
mesenchymal cells that form the pericardium and the septum
心膜と中隔を形成する間葉系細胞
transversum, so both the relationship
横隔膜。つまり、関係性も
with my heart and my diaphragm, the developing brain will wrap around the
私の心臓と横隔膜、発達する脳は、
heart, we see
心臓の周りに巻き付くでしょう。
that the amniotic cavity comes to push all around and in the center it
羊膜腔が周囲全体を押し、中心ではそれが
will
私の血管を脊索の前に集めるでしょう。
The growth rate between this pure mesodermal cardiac tube which
この純粋な中胚葉性心臓管の間の成長速度は、
is both the motor
成長の原動力であると同時に、
for growth but at the same time the organizer of my growth becomes a field of
私の成長のオーガナイザーでもあるものが、ある種の制限の場となる。
restriction
制限
in relation to the amniotic cavity which pushes like this
羊膜腔に対して、このように押されるが、
but which is informed by my neural
私の神経管によって情報が与えられ、それが最も多くの情報を受け取る。
tube which receives the greatest information.
神経管が最も速く成長し、胚を心臓の周りで屈曲運動させる。
grows the fastest and causes the embryo to make a flexion movement around the
心臓の周りで屈曲運動させる。
heart.
心臓。
But so the heart, in fact, is always in its place.
しかし、心臓は実際には常にその場所にある。
It's the system that wraps around it.
その周りに巻き付くのはシステムである。
And in this process, there is only one thing, which is that I have a slowed growth rate
そしてこの過程では、唯一のことは、成長速度が遅くなり、
and a drawing together of fluids from the outside, from the periphery, towards
そして、外部、つまり周辺から中心へと体液が近づくことである。
the center.
中心へ。
That's why we see here that the cephalization movement will lead to
そのため、ここで見られるように、頭部化の動きが
the cardialization space
心臓化の空間
which will gradually lead to
それが少しずつ
diaphragmatization
横隔膜化
and we will see later
そして後で見るように
what is called hepatization
肝臓化と呼ばれるもの
and as we progress
そして進むにつれて
we will see that this hepatization
この肝臓化が
will actually lead to adrenalization
実際には副腎化を引き起こし、
which will lead to
それが引き起こすのは
gonadization
性腺化
and so I have a whole movement
したがって、私は全体的な動きを持っている。
here of very interesting development
ここに非常に興味深い発達があり、
which is linked to the development
それは発達に関連している。
of my amniotic cavity
私の羊膜腔の
which will
それは
Completely wrap what I call zone B, you see.
私がBゾーンと呼ぶものを完全に包み込むだろう。
Cephalization leads to cardialization, which will lead to diaphragmatization,
頭部化は心臓化を引き起こし、それが横隔膜化を引き起こし、
which will lead to the entire posterior part of the peritoneal cavity.
それが腹膜腔の後部全体を引き起こす。
The entire movement of the median line, for example in women, which will form the uterus and fallopian tubes.
例えば女性の場合、子宮と卵管を形成する正中線の動き全体。
And in men, a movement that will not go all the way, but which will form their prostate on the median plane.
そして男性の場合、最後まで行かないが、正中面で前立腺を形成する動き。
Then, it will come back to this part here, and I will have the whole system.
その後、それはここの部分に戻り、私はシステム全体を持つことになる。
of the perineum that will develop here and a return to this
ここで発達する会陰の、そしてこの
tilt here which is actually a
ここでの傾きへの回帰、それは実際には
rebalancing of my liver which at that moment will make its tilt and this lateral
私の肝臓の再均衡であり、実際にはその時点で肝臓が傾き、この動きが
movement, the
横方向の
liver becomes a great source of organization for my entire development and the
肝臓は私の発達全体と組織化の大きな源となる。
closure
閉鎖
of my anterior median line. What is important to remember here is that I have a
私の前正中線が。ここで覚えておくべき重要なことは、私が
drawing together towards my median line and that the heart first develops towards this anterior median
正中線に向かって近づいていること、そして心臓がまずこの前正中線に向かって発達することです。
line.
前方の
But at the same time, I have an important process of cephalization.
しかし同時に、私は重要な頭部形成のプロセスを持っています。
In yellow is the amniotic cavity.
黄色は羊膜腔です。
In blue, the ectoderm, the developing brain.
青は外胚葉、発達中の脳です。
Then I have another area here, the heart.
そしてここに別の領域、心臓があります。
And there, the diaphragmatic zone that comes to integrate here,
そしてそこに、ここに統合される横隔膜領域があり、
with the gradual integration of my vitelline vesicle,
私の卵黄嚢が徐々に統合され、
which will gradually meet on what is called the embryonic pedicle
それは胚柄と呼ばれるものの上で徐々に合流し、
to form the umbilical cord.
へその緒を形成します。
So all this is a developmental movement.
したがって、これらすべては発達上の動きです。
With a very interesting zone, it's my amniotic cavity that will organize
非常に興味深い領域は、これらすべてを組織する私の羊膜腔です。
all this.
これらすべてを。
Finally, it's a balance between the aortic system,
最終的には、大動脈系、
so the vascular axis, and the amniotic cavity.
つまり血管軸と羊膜腔との間のバランスです。
You see the heart that is here, there.
ここにある心臓が見えますか。
Finally, it's the brain that came around.
最終的には、脳がその周りに来ました。
So I have a movement like that.
だから私はこのような動きをします。
I have this integration, and then I will have a movement that will do this.
この統合があり、そして私はこのような動きをします。
To form the diaphragm, all the part of
横隔膜を形成するために、
posterior parietal peritoneum, and then it comes back around.
後方の壁側腹膜のすべてが、そしてそれは周りに戻ってきます。
If I put my hands back in this position, I put it above, this becomes a fulcrum, it
この位置で手を再び取ると、それを上に置くと、これが支点になり、それは
does this.
これを行います。
I'm doing it backwards.
私は逆さまにやっています。
A fulcrum that we will study, it will be in relation to the heart, in relation to the brain.
私たちが研究する支点は、心臓に関して、脳に関してです。
In relation to the origin, I put myself coccyx, brain
起源に関して、私は尾骨、脳、
and heart here.
そしてここに心臓を置きます。
So there, I am in its embryonic sketch, if you will.
だから私は今、その胚の初期段階にいる、と言ってもいいでしょう。
It depends if you take a notochord, your coccyx or not.
あなたがオートコレ、あなたの尾骨を取るかどうかによります。
There, I just took the primitive streak.
ここでは、原始線だけを取りました。
That can already lead me to something quite important,
それはすでに私にかなり重要な何かをもたらすことができます、
because the line can be deviated at birth,
なぜなら線は出生時にずれる可能性があり、
it can be deviated at conception, it can be deviated in the pre-coccyx.
受胎時にずれる可能性があり、前尾骨期にずれる可能性があります。
ceptual.
概念的な。
It's worth seeing where you can reconnect.
どこに再接続できるかを見る価値があります。
To give information,
情報を提供するために、
whether it's in a word,
それが言葉であろうと、
in a gesture, or in a presence,
ジェスチャーであろうと、存在であろうと、
or in something that the body must express to me.
あるいは体が私に表現しなければならないものの中に。
the brain and the heart,
脳と心は、
they know each other well.
お互いをよく知っています。
The heart was there.
心はそこにありました。
But it hasn't moved.
しかし、彼は動きませんでした。
Little by little,
少しずつ、
this notion, it's my amniotic cavity
この概念は、私の羊膜腔が
that forms
形成されることです
in this movement?
この動きの中で？
It's a work we're going to do
これは私たちが行う作業です
on zone B.
Bゾーンについて。
We will also integrate the lateral forces.
側方力も統合します。
So the force of delimitation
したがって、境界の力
thoraco-abdominal
胸腹部の
in the integration of the system
システムの統合において
circulatory from the periphery
末梢からの循環
towards the center. That way, we'll have the whole movement.
中心へ。そうすれば、すべての動きが得られます。
Zone B, for me,
Bゾーンは、私にとって、
in this integration here, it will be the amniotic cavity.
ここでのこの統合では、羊膜腔になります。
If you have a baby here,
ここに赤ちゃんがいる場合、
you float
あなたは浮いています
in your amniotic cavity.
あなたの羊膜腔の中に。
This envelope will disappear at the membrane level, but the energetic aspect is there.
この膜は膜レベルでは消えますが、エネルギー的な側面はそこにあります。
This kind of bubble around you that you need. If you already see it in the integration
あなたが必要とするあなたの周りのこの種の球体。あなたがすでに統合の中でそれを見ているなら、
of this, this amniotic cavity, from its beginning, it forms your neural
この羊膜腔は、その初期段階から、あなたの神経管を形成しています。
tube. It is
それは、
integrated into your neural tube. That means that when you have a whiplash, when you have a problem
あなたの神経管に統合されています。つまり、むち打ち症や問題がある場合、
of a dysfunction at the cranio-sacral level, or on the core
頭蓋仙骨レベルでの機能不全、またはコア
links.
リンク。
or whatever, if you can't put it back, go before, treat
あるいは何であれ、元に戻せない場合は、まず、
the amniotic cavity,
羊膜腔を治療し、
restore the spaces between sacrum, heart, and you redo the whole movement and you see where it blocks,
仙骨と心臓の間の空間を再構築し、すべての動きをやり直して、どこでブロックされているかを確認し、
and then you can rework, and you let the system work in this recognition of neutrals,
そして、あなたは再作業することができ、システムが中立の認識の中で機能することを許可します。
or else you can do it yourself, and then you work on the lateral
あるいは、自分でそれを行うこともでき、そしてあなたはプロセスに取り組むことができます
processes, but we'll see those again.
横方向の、しかしそれらは後で再検討します。
A cross-section.
横断面。
I have my amniotic cavity, a neural groove, so the fluid that is here, which is primitive
私には羊膜腔、神経溝があります。したがって、ここにある液体は、原始的な羊水であり、
amniotic fluid, until it forms a neural tube.
それが神経管を形成するまでです。
It will be integrated into this tube.
それはこの管に統合されます。
There is the closure of my anterior neuropore and my posterior neuropore, that is, on the 28th
私の前部神経孔と後部神経孔の閉鎖があります。つまり、28日目です。
day, this tube is closed.
日、この管は閉じています。
You should rather really focus on zone B, because it is the one that integrates your
ゾーンBに本当に集中すべきです。なぜなら、そこがあなたの
CSF.
LCRを統合するからです。
It's not the other way around.
逆ではありません。
It appears when you...
それは、あなたが...
enters the mucosa, this embryo, I have the embryonic button and at the moment it enters the
この胚が粘膜に入ると、胚芽ボタンがあり、粘膜に入った瞬間に、ここに滲出液が現れます。そして、これがあなたの
mucosa here I have an exudate that appears here and this is my amniotic cavity that will create
神経管、神経板、消化管を形成する羊膜腔です。機能的な観点から、私のエピブラストをこの腔から分離することはできません。それは常に統合されています。
your
あなたの
neural tube, your neural plate and your digestive tube. I cannot separate on
神経管、神経板、消化管。機能的な観点から、私のエピブラストをこの腔から分離することはできません。それは常に統合されています。
a functional
機能的な
plane my epiblast from this cavity, it is always integrated.
機能的な観点から、私のエピブラストをこの腔から分離することはできません。それは常に統合されています。
You will have this external
この外部体腔は、胚の発生運動によって体腔に統合されます。
an external coelom into a large part of an internal coelom and the rest will leave as
外部体腔の大部分は内部体腔に、残りは外部に滲出液として排出されます。それは羊膜腔によって押し戻されます。
exudates outside. It is pushed back by the amniotic cavity. In
滲出液として外部に排出されます。それは羊膜腔によって押し戻されます。成長において、
growth,
成長において、
so at some point, it no longer develops. That is, you had the neurontic
ある時点で、それはもはや発達しません。つまり、卵黄嚢と羊膜腔の間の情報である神経腸管がありました。
canal which is an information between the vitelline vesicle and
卵黄嚢と
the amniotic cavity.
羊膜腔の間の情報である神経腸管がありました。
Nothing to do with the external coelom. The external coelom will be integrated
外部体腔とは関係ありません。外部体腔は、
into an internal coelom
内部体腔に統合され、
to form.
形成されます。
The peritoneal cavity.
腹膜腔。
But at some point, there will be no more growth of this cavity.
しかし、ある時点で、この腔の成長は止まります。
So we have the impression that it will be pushed back.
だから、押し戻されるように見えます。
But no, there was a liter, but the other grows so much and in the growth that finally, it's an exudate.
いや、1リットルあったのですが、もう一方が非常に大きく成長し、成長の過程で、結局それは滲出液になります。
Except that it will have integrated the external coelom into an internal coelom.
ただし、外部体腔を内部体腔に統合したという点を除いては。